She's pretty.
Yes, it is.
So...
This time
Ushimi and Maiko.
It's been a while.
So cute!
Too cute!
Really.
Why are they so cute?
LOL!
So, what a surprise, Woo-chan will celebrate her 4th birthday on October 10!
Happy birthday, Woo-chan!
I was also born in October, so we are all October-born friends.
Today, in celebration of her birthday, we went out to take her first birthday photo.
We went to Rock Photo Studio to take her first birthday photo!
It's raining, so be careful not to get Woo-chan wet!
Boo boo!
Let's get right to it. Shall we go in, Woo-chan?
Let's go in, shall we?
I'm going to go get a very cute picture of you. Let's go, U-chan!
So today we're here at Rock Portrait Rion, and we're looking forward to working with you today.
Today is her birthday, so she is decorated with birthday repotations.
I'm going to take a picture of Moeko and Boo-chan in it.
Me too? Can I come too?
Is it OK?
It's going to be an anniversary today, isn't it?
I'm so happy. I'm looking forward to seeing you.
I cherish the photos of Woo-chan, Moeko-san and Woo-chan's Monikyu-sho very much.
Thank you very much.
I would like to do my best to deepen our relationship since our last meeting.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Next notice
Ucchan, over here, over here!
Ucchan, over here, over here, come on, come on, come on, come on!
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on!
Come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here!
Thank you, guardian.
Yes, yes, yes!
Department However
Bee
I feel like I can talk to Ucchan more friendly.
I feel like I can talk more friendly with Ucchan 나면
많아
Arguer
Nasu
That's a yes.
Remember when you were 4 years old?
Will you still be friends with Moe?
Ha!
Happy Birthday Woo Chan
Happy birthday Dear.
Wu Chan.
Chan.
There it is!
Happy Birthday Woo Chan
Yeah, yeah, okay.
Yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So cute!
I was able to celebrate a lot in the time I spent feeling Buchan's warmth.
He is cute.
I'm going to get Buchan now.
I'll have you take a cute picture of him.
Too cute!
Wait.
Excuse me.
Wait, Woo-chan!
That's great.
Wait, wait, wait
That's what I've been trying to tell you.
Woo-chan is suddenly cheerful
So now...
The first pattern.
Ah, it's over!
The shooting is over.
Now
She's changing the set.
But since it's Woo-chan's birthday...
I have something to give her.
Yes, I have.
Will you accept it?
Yes, ma'am.
Here it is.
That's it!
clap clap clap
This is it.
I'd like to give you a birthday present.
Happy birthday, Woo-chan!
I'd like to show you
I'd like to show you what I prepared as a birthday present for Woo-chan.
First of all, sweets!
Woo-chan's favorite sweet potato!
Ah, here's Woo-chan!
Do you like sweet potatoes, Woo-chan?
Here's a sweet potato for you, Woo-chan!
Here's a present for you, Woo-chan.
I have one too.
Boo-chan likes sweet potatoes, too.
Eat this, Buchan, and grow up!
I want to give you two presents.
I'd like to give you two. Sit down. Can you sit down?
Sit! Sit!
Oh, good boy! You're such a good boy! Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
Okay! First time!
Aah! Aah! Aah! Would it be better if it was on its side?
Can you keep this up already? Oh!
He's eating!
Yes!
Buchan ate it!
But I kind of want him to go away just by looking at him like this.
I'd like to go on to the next present!
Next...
This one
These clothes!
Woo-chan!
Isn't that Woo-chan?
It has an illustration of a dog on it.
Red looks great on you. It really does.
I love red.
I think she'll be even cuter.
I hope Wu-chan will come. Oh, she's back.
Welcome home, Wu. It was delicious.
I'm curious. Look, Wu-chan.
Look, Wu-chan. Look at your new outfit.
Wu-chan's wearing the summery pineapple outfit I gave her at the last Shimi-Toyuko event.
It's the pineapple summery outfit I gave Wu-chan in the last Shimi-Tomoyuko Vol. 1, but it's going to get a little colder.
I thought it would be nice to make the material a little warmer and keep her warmer.
I'm sure she'll be able to spend more time in the warmth of this material.
Next, toys!
Here are the toys. Nice to meet you.
Here's a bunny and a cabana. They're already very interested. It's perfect.
I'll take it off now. I'll do it. Wait a minute.
Let's play with the bunny.
Great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great.
That's great.
Ui-chan.
Where do you want to go?
Oh!
That's great!
He's become your favorite, hasn't he?
Good night!
I'm going!
Can I go?
LOL.
Laughing.
I want to go for the last present!
I'm sure you'll be very happy, Mi-chan.
Look!
Ta-da!
I still don't know what it is.
Cake!
They're so curious!
It's chilled to the bone.
Let's open it up!
This is a vegetable birthday cake.
Doggies can eat it!
A doggie cake.
Let's open it.
Ready?
Tori!
Happy Birthday!
Happy birthday to you!
Yu-chan, what's this?
After a hard day's shooting
For your enjoyment
I'll take a picture of it.
Okay.
Okay, then.
So that we can eat it together.
Let's work hard on the rest of the shoot.
Good night.
Hey, Woo-chan, over here!
Come here, Woo-chan. Come here, come here.
Come here, boy.
Hey, Woo-chan, over here!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Good, good, good.
That's great.
You're so cute!
Woo-chan!
Woo-hoo!
Oh?
Hmm?
Uh-oh!
Woo-chan!
Thank you for looking at me!
Oh?
Woo-chan!
Suddenly
I think I may have found a new skill.
I like your voice.
I'm happy if U-chan enjoys herself.
I feel like I'm missing something important
Let's go for the solo for the last time
Ucchan, it's your solo time.
Sit down, Utchan.
Sit down, Ucchan!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
Good boy! Good boy!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
You're a good boy! You're a good boy!
Aah!
Boo-boo.
Yes, sir.
Yeah. - Yeah.
That's good.
Chicks.
Hi.
So cute!
Hey, Boo!
Good job!
You did great.
You did a great job
you did a great job
There are so many of them
go on and on and on
Take a look
Oh, my gosh!
Buchan is looking at me.
I have a picture.
I'm looking at you, too.
Can we do this?
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
I think we can.
I'll keep looking and looking.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
More and more.
Go, go, go, go, go, go.
Wow, I'm surrounded by balloons!
Oh, I'm so happy!
Thank you for your hard work, Buchanan!
Oh, hey...
I'm kind of grinning.
You really took a lot of pictures.
I'd like to look at them one by one and choose one.
This way, everyone!
What do you think?
Here is a shot of Woo-chan's 4th birthday as my lovey-dovey shot!
My face is overflowing with love for Woo-chan!
I'm so happy that we were able to spend Woo-chan's important birthday together like this.
I'm so happy that we were able to celebrate your birthday together.
I even got Woo-chan to wear the outfit I gave her earlier!
It looks so cute on her!
Today
I felt that our bond with Roo-chan has deepened even more.
I'm so happy!
I'm so happy that you guys commented on it.
I'd love it if you all commented on it or commented on it.
there may be a third installment, so...
Thank you for working so hard today, Roo-chan!
I'm looking forward to seeing you soon!
That's all for now.
This is the second installment of Ushimi and Tomoeko!
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching!